# **Robert James Wraight**

British Columbia, Canada

Email: rwraight32@gmail.com

Portfolio: www.bobbywdev.com

## **Profile:**

Experience working in a customer service, team based environment as well as individual positions at various levels of employment and in a wide range of roles.
 Completed and presented projects and websites using a variety of languages and technologies including HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, MySql, Nodejs, Mongodb, Firebase Database, npm, Bootstrap, SASS, SCSS, Autoprefixer, Ajax, and APIs, amongst others.

□ Experience working in administrative, retail, management, production, serving, warehouse, government, and logistic roles.

# **Education:**

Selkirk College - Nelson, B.C

Certificate in Web Development – May 2022

Kwantlen Polytechnic University - Surrey, B.C

Bachelor of Arts Major in Anthropology – Dec 2014

# **Employment:**

# Parallel 49 Brewing Company - Vancouver, B.C

Assistant General Manager – Feb 2017-June 2020

- Responsible for opening or closing of the brewery on a daily basis. Constructing floor plans for staff each shift. Managing the operation of the Street Kitchen and Tasting Room on a daily basis. Responsible for ensuring proper policies and procedures are followed by staff as well as training staff.
- Maintaining employee files in regards to certification, employment paperwork, writeups, filed complaints, as well as hiring and interviewing of potential employees.
- Responsible for merchandise, Sysco, inventory, maintenance, coin, keg, and warehouse orders.
   Computer work related to inventory, product waste, unpaid tabs, staff walkouts, ordering, customer inquiries, and email correspondence.

 Managing clear avenues of communication between front and back of house employees, ownership, warehouse, distribution, production, sales, marketing, and maintenance teams.
 Responsible for direct communication with customers, and accounts regarding product rentals, reservations, events, product knowledge, returns, refunds, and complaints.

## **Crossborder Vehicles - Surrey, B.C**

Supervisor/Team Lead - April 2016-December 2016

- Supervising a team to ensure the efficient and effective examination of vehicles being shipped into the United States from Canada.
- Responsible for accurate data entry, scheduling of repairs and recall issues, interacting with clients face to face and over the telephone on a daily basis, accurate inventory, proper completion of paperwork, and working with a group in a supervisory role.
- Ensure vehicles being shipped across the border into the United States meet the requirements
  necessary for importation and use within the United States. Ensure vehicles also meet the
  standards of Crossborder Vehicles policies as well as the client's and customer's requirements
  for satisfaction.

## Canada Border Services Agency – Abbotsford, B.C

Administrative Assistant/Traveler Services Representative - April 2012-May 2015

- Reference and apply tax and duty laws regarding personal and commercial goods importation into Canada.
- Lead on special projects including the archiving and documentation of sensitive documents.
- Responsible for accurate data input and form completion regarding consumer goods and vehicle importation, visitor and immigration statistics, and revenue for the Government of Canada.
- Responsible for general office duties, including but not limited to, directing and assisting clients
  by telephone, accepting payments using POS, faxing and mailing documents containing sensitive
  information, sorting and archiving of documents, and correspondence with various branches of
  the agency and government.

#### **Certifications:**

Certificate of Web Development with Honors – May 2022

Bachelor of Arts Degree in Anthropology – Dec 2014